[{
        "Question": "Select question to ask",
        "Answer": ""
    },{
        "Question": "What do you see?",
        "Answer": "A yellow block is below the purple block. A red block is below the yellow block. A blue loc_c location is below the red block. A purple block is on the yellow block. A yellow block is on the red block. A red block is on the blue loc_c location. I see a green loc_a location and a green loc_b location"  
}, {
        "Question": "What is below the purple block 3?",
        "Answer": "A yellow block."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is below the yellow block 2?",
        "Answer": "A red block."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is below the red block 1?",
        "Answer": "A blue loc_c location."
    }, { 
        "Question": "What is on the green loc_a location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the green loc_b location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the blue loc_c location?",
        "Answer": "A red block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the red block 1?",
        "Answer": "A yellow block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the yellow block 2?",
        "Answer": "A purple block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the purple block 3?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the purple block 3.",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The color is purple. The volume is 1.0 . A yellow block is below the purple block."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the yellow block 2.",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The color is yellow. The volume is 2.0 . A red block is below the yellow block. A purple block is on the yellow block."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the red block 1.",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The color is red. The volume is 3.0 . A blue loc_c location is below the red block. A yellow block is on the red block. "
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the green loc_a location.",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is green. The volume is 4.0 ."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the green loc_b location.",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is green. The volume is 4.0 ."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the blue loc_c location.",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is blue. The volume is 4.0 . A red block is on the blue loc_c location. "
}]
